{
    "0":
    {
        "question": "Wrong level bro. Type 'heya' in answer to continue",
        "answer": "level1",
        "time": 60
    },
    "1":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level1",
        "time": 60
    },
    "2":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level2",
        "time": 60
    },
    "3":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level3",
        "time": 60
    },
    "4":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level4",
        "time": 60
    },
    "5":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level5",
        "time": 60
    },
    "6":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level6",
        "time": 60
    },
    "7":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level7",
        "time": 60
    },
    "8":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level8",
        "time": 60
    },
    "9":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level9",
        "time": 60
    },
    "10":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level10",
        "time": 60
    },
    "11":
    {
        "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.",
        "answer": "level11",
        "time": 60
    }
}
